{
    "subject": "resource/Fabula_Nova_Crystallis_Final_Fantasy",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "resource/PlayStation_4",
    "human_readable": "Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available on PlayStation 4.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9842928051948547,
            "question": "Besides PlayStation 4, are there any other platforms where Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9594476222991943,
            "question": "Is Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy a PlayStation exclusive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9241465926170349,
            "question": "On which gaming platform can you play Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8867107033729553,
            "question": "What type of game is Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8321207165718079,
            "question": "What is the name of the gaming franchise that includes Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118987679481506,
            "question": "What year was Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8002150654792786,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7782211303710938,
            "question": "What is the plot of Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687522768974304,
            "question": "Does Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy have any notable features or gameplay mechanics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7599798440933228,
            "question": "Does Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy have any sequels or spin-offs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available on PlayStation 4.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4643_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy have any notable features or gameplay mechanics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4643_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4643_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main characters in Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4643_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4643_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention any availability of Fabula Nova Crystallis games on PlayStation 4. They only reference platforms such as PLAYSTATION\u00ae3, mobile phones, and PSP for some titles within the series. There is no information provided about PlayStation 4 in the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy was initially developed for PlayStation 3, PSP, and mobile phones. There's no information provided to suggest that any of the titles within this series have been released or announced for the PlayStation 4.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context states that Fabula Nova Crystallis encompasses titles for PlayStation 3, mobile phones and Xbox 360. There is no mention of PlayStation 4.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of the PlayStation 4 in any part of the provided context information, which discusses the development and release of Fabula Nova Crystallis titles for platforms such as the PlayStation 3 computer entertainment system, mobile phones, PSP, PS3, Xbox 360.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions development for Fabula Nova Crystallis titles on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and mobile phones, but there is no mention of availability on PlayStation 4.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}